Now, thinking about the room itself, we have a number of options.
现在关于房间，我们有很多选择。
You can have a single study bedroom or you can have a shared one.
你可以选择一间单人房也可以和别人共享。
These are both what we call simple rooms.
这就是我们说的简易房。
The other alternative is to opt for a single bedsit which actually has more space and better facilities.
另一种选择是单人小套房，它的空间更大，设施更好。
There's about ￡20 a week difference between them.
这两者之间一周相差大约20英镑。
Well, actually my grant is quite generous and I think the bedsit sounds the best option.
事实上，我的补助金很多，我想小套房是最好的选择。
Lovely. I'll put you down for that and we'll see what availability is like.
很好。我帮你记下，看看有没有可以住的。
Now can I ask some other personal details which we like to have on record? Yes, of course.
现在我能问你一些需要记录的个人问题吗？当然。
I wonder if you could let us know what your interests are.
你能否告诉我们你的兴趣是什么，
This might help us get a closer match for placing you in a particular hall.
这能帮我们为你找到最适合的公寓。
Well. I love the theatre. Right.
嗯，我喜欢戏剧。好的。
And I enjoy sports, particularly badminton. That's worth knowing.
我喜欢运动，特别是羽毛球。了解到这点很好。
Well, the first thing is I'd prefer a hall where there are other mature students, if possible.
如果可以的话，首先我更喜欢宿舍里有其他的成年学生。
Yes, we do have halls which tend to cater for slightly older students.
是的。我们通常有招待年纪稍长一点的学生的宿舍。
Ummm, Ah, and I'd prefer to be out of town.
我更想住在城外。
That's actually very good for you because we tend to have more vacancies in out-of -town halls.
其实这对你来说很好，因为我们在城外有更多的宿舍空缺。
Lucky! Yes. Angthing else?
真走运！是的，还有什么要求吗？
Well, I would like somewhere with a shared area, a TV room for example, or something like that.It's a good way to socialise.
我希望有一个共享区域，例如电视机房之类的。这是社交的好方法。。
It certainly is. That's it.
当然。就是这些。
Now, we just need a contact telephone number for you.
现在，我们需要知道你的联系电话。
Sure, I'll just find it.It's double 67549.
当然。我找找。667549。
Great, so we'll be in contact with you as soon as possible...
好极了，那么我们会尽快联系你……